Guide to the Walter Isard papers, 1938-1986.
Isard, Walter papers
- Financial Records Book, 1971 (Box 39, Folder Item 15)
- Financial Records Book, 1972-1975 (Box 39, Folder Item 16)
- Philadelphia Region Input-Output Coefficient Table, Oversized Tables 1-9 (Box 40, Folder Item 1)
- Oversized negatives of NY Central Region Survey Maps 1-10, USGS NY map (Box 40, Folder Item 2)
- Program 29th N. American Meetings of RSA, Pittsburgh 1982 Brochure, 1982 (Box 41, Folder Item 1)
- Southeastern RSA Selected Papers Publication--Knoxville, TN, 1968 (Box 41, Folder Item 2)
  RSA journal
- RSA 29th Annual N. American Meeting Abstracts, 1982--Pittsburgh, 1982 (Box 41, Folder Item 3)
- RSA Papers Vol. 25, 1970--Santa Monica Meeting 1969, 1970 (Box 41, Folder Item 4)
- RSA Papers Vol. 15--1965, 1965 (Box 41, Folder Item 5)
- RSA Papers Vol. 19--1967, 1967 (Box 41, Folder Item 6)
- RSA Papers Vol. 17--1966, 1966 (Box 41, Folder Item 7)
- RSA Papers Vol. 18--1967, 1967 (Box 41, Folder Item 8)
- RSA Papers Vol. 16--1966, 1966 (Box 41, Folder Item 9)
- RSA Papers Vol. 14--1965, 1965 (Box 41, Folder Item 10)
- RSA Papers Vol. 31--1973, 1973 (Box 41, Folder Item 11)
- RSA Papers Vol. 30--1973, 1973 (Box 41, Folder Item 12)
- RSA Papers Vol. 29--1972, 1972 (Box 41, Folder Item 13)
- RSA Papers Vol. 28--1972, 1972 (Box 41, Folder Item 14)
- RSA Papers Vol. 27--1971, 1971 (Box 41, Folder Item 15)
- RSA Papers Vol. 26--1970, 1970 (Box 41, Folder Item 16)
- RSA Papers Vol. 24--1970, 1970 (Box 41, Folder Item 17)
- International Regional Science Rw. Vol. 7--1982, 1982 (Box 41, Folder Item 18)
  International Regional Science Review publication
- RSA Papers Vol. 12--1964, 1964 (Box 41, Folder Item 19)
- RSA Papers Vol. 13--1964, 1964 (Box 41, Folder Item 20)
- RSA Papers Vol. 7--1961, 1961 (Box 41, Folder Item 21)
- RSA Papers Vol. 6--1960, 1960 (Box 41, Folder Item 22)
- RSA Papers Vol. 5--1959, 1959 (Box 41, Folder Item 23)
- RSA Papers Vol. 10--1963, 1963 (Box 41, Folder Item 24)
- RSA Papers Vol. 11--1963, 1963 (Box 41, Folder Item 25)
- RSA Papers Vol. 8--1962, 1962 (Box 41, Folder Item 26)
- RSA Papers Vol. 9--1962, 1962 (Box 41, Folder Item 27)
- RSA Papers Vol.22--1969, 1969 (Box 41, Folder Item 28)
- RSA Papers Vol.20--1968, 1968 (Box 41, Folder Item 29)
- RSA Papers Vol.21--1968, 1968 (Box 41, Folder Item 30)
- RSA Papers Vol.33--1974, 1974 (Box 41, Folder Item 31)
- RSA Papers Vol.32--1974, 1974 (Box 41, Folder Item 32)
- RSA Papers Vol.23--1969, 1969 (Box 41, Folder Item 33)
- RSA Papers and Proceedings Vol. 4, 1958, 1958 (Box 41, Folder Item 34)
- RSA Papers and Proceedings Vol. 1, 1955, 1955 (Box 41, Folder Item 35)
- RSA Papers and Proceedings Vol. 2, 1956, 1956 (Box 41, Folder Item 36)
- RSA Papers and Proceedings Vol. 3, 1956, 1957 (Box 41, Folder Item 37)
- Soviet Union: A Geographical Survey Book, 1976 (Box 41, Folder Item 38)
- Jan. 1973 - April 30, 1973, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  General Correspondence
- Oct. 2, 1972 - December 22, 1972, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- May - September, 1972, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Jan. 1972 - April 1972, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Aug. 1971 - Dec. 1971, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- May - July 1971, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- April - Jan. 1971, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Sept. - Dec. 1970, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- WI's Correspondence 1974-1976 + some other years, 1974-1976 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Jan. - June 1975, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Aug. - Dec. 1974, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Jan. - July 1974, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- May - Dec. 1973, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- April - June 1976, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- January - April 1976, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Sept.- Dec. 1975 Correspondence, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- July - October 1975, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- December 1976 - January 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- October - December 1976, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- August - October 1976, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Letters Mailed Sept. 1978 - May 1979, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- December 1980 - February 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- October - December 1980, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- June - October 1980, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Letters Mailed Jan. 1978 - Aug. 1978, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Letters Mailed Sept. - Dec. 1977, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Chronological File 3/81 - 7/81, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Chronological File Jan. - May 1980, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Chronological File June - Dec. 1979, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Chronological File Jan. - May 1979 + Some from 1978, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- RSA Meeting--Conference November 1977, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- RSA Newsletter 1977 January, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- RSA Newsletter May 1977, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- RSA Newsletter Sept. 1977, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- RSA Newsletter Jan. 1976, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- RSA Newsletter January, May, August 1975, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- RSA Newsletter January, May, August 1974, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- RSA Newsletter May 1973, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- RSA Newsletter Jan., May 1972, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- RSA Newsletter August, January 1971, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- RSA Newsletter April 1970, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- RSA Newsletters Dec., August, May 1969, Programs 1969, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- RSA Newsletters January, May, August, December 1968, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- RSA Newsletters January, May, August 1967, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- RSA 1950-1959 Newsletters, Programs, Papers, etc., 1950-1959 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Isard Correspondence Jan. - Dec. 1985, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- RSA & Regional Science Sept.--Constitutions, Programs, etc., 1956-1962 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- PSS(I) 1963-1972, 1963-1972 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- PSS(I) 1978 W. Section Stanford Mtg., Officers 1969- 1974, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- PSS(I) Newsletter, Constitutions, Publications, Misc.--1973-1974, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Thesis--Theories of Urban Externalities, Yoshi Kanemoto, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Marcia Will, PhD. Thesis (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Thesis--Evolutionary Change in Hierarchical Systems: A General Theory, Phyllis C. Kaniss, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Regional Science Dissertation & Monograph Series #5--A Dynamic Interindustry Model for the Economic Analysis of Air Pollution Abatement, Adam Zachary Rose, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Regional Science Dissertation & Monograph Series #6--Poor Regions in Rich Societies, Anders Dedekam, Jr., 1977 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Thesis--An Information Management Framework for Policy Analysis in Small Nations, Bruce Griffith Burton, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Thesis--Multivariate Analysis of Rural Emigration of Labor in W. Central Mexico, J. Jesus Arroyo Alejandre, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Thesis--Estimation of Spatial Autoregressive Structures: A Contribution to Spatial Econometrics, Luc Eugene Anselin, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Thesis--Theories and Models of Residential Spatial Structure in Mutli-Center Urban Areas, Michalis Constas Romanos, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Thesis--A Study of Interregional Capital Movements, Iwan J. Azis, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Thesis--Our Changing Evolution: Strategies for 1980, Leonard Starobin, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Published Journals--Man Environment Space & Time 1979-1988 and Newsletter of the World Univ. of the World Academy of Art and Science, No. 1-4, 1979-1988 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Harvard--Administrative Arrangements 1966-1972 #1 of 3, 1966-72 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Harvard--Administrative Arrangements 1966-1972 #2 of 3, 1966-1972 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Harvard--Administrative Arrangements 1966-1972 #3 of 3, 1966-1972 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Dissertation--Stochastic Control and Multilevel Coordination Models For Air Quality Management Within a Region, Abdo Ovadia Salama, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Thesis--Market Systems for the Control of Air Pollution, William David Montogomery, III, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Global Economic Modeling, NSF Proposals, etc. 1986-87, 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- CMPS Journal Correspondence 1986-1990 #1 of 2, 1986-1990 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- CMPS Journal Correspondence 1986-1990 #2 of 2, 1986-1990 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Peace Science Conference 1981 Kyoto--Publication of book 1982-83, 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Harvard-Yale-MIT-Penn Peace Science Seminar 1975, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Harvard-Yale-MIT-Penn Peace Science Seminar 1971-1974, 1971-1974 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Harvard-Yale-MIT-Penn Peace Science Seminar 1970-1971, 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Harvard-Yale-MIT-Penn Seminar Environmental--Int'l 1974 #1 of 3, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Harvard-Yale-MIT-C-P Environmental Issues--Int'l 1974 #2 of 3, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Harvard-Yale-MIT-C-P Environmental Issues--Int'l 1974-1975 #3 of 3, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Joint Center Harvard MIT Seminar 1975-79 #1 of 2, 1975-1979 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Joint Center Harvard MIT Seminar 1975-79 #2 of 2, 1974-1979 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Policy Science Seminar, Upenn 1975-79 # 1of 2, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Policy Science Seminar, Upenn 1975-79 # 2of 2, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Faculty Peace Science Seminar--Cornell 1977, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Harvard CIFA Peace Science Seminar 1978, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Hierarchy Seminar--Harvard 1978, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Global Economic Modeling, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Hiroshima Conference, August 18-19 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Poznan Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Tsukuba, Japan, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  World Academy of Art and Sciences
- Tokyo, Japan, 1976-1978 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Conference--2nd. Tsukuba, 1981, 1978-1981 (Box 48, Folder 5a)
- 4th Tokyo 1981, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 5b)
- Conference--Japan, PSS(I), 1981, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 5c)
- International Institute for Peace, Vienna, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- PSSI Mannheim September 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Warsaw Conference in Regional Sociology--Sept.1977, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- RSA Cracow 1977 August, European, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- RSA American Northeast Halifax 1977, 1973-1977 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- RSA Toronto, Ontario Nov 12-14, 1976, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- 2nd Tokyo Transport Environmental Conference, August 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- W.U. Norukura Seminar Japan, August 9-16, 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Cornell University--April 25, 1976, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  Northeast RSA meeting
- Rutgers University--April 19-21, 1974, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  Northeast RSA conference
- Univ. of Pennsylvania--Nov. 10, 1972, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Univ. of Michigan--Nov. 12-174, 1971, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Syracuse Univ.--April 27-29, 1973, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- The 3rd Tokyo Transport Environmental Conference--August 23-25, 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- PSSI Hiroshima--Aug. 18-19, 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- PSSI Philadelphia--Nov. 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- PSSI Geneva Sept. 3-5, 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Europe RSA February 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- W.U. Conference--Tsukuba Aug. 21-23, 1978, World Regional Development + Planning Conference, 1976-1978 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Poznan Sept. 7-9, 1978; W.U. World Health Conference, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- PSSI--16th N. American Conference, Chicago-November 13-15, 1978, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- PSSI Miscellaneous 1978, 1975-1978 (Box 48, Folder 27)
- RSA: Regional Science Association London Meeting 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- PSSI Berlin 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- RSA European London 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- RSA Chicago Nov. 1978, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Australia Pacific RSA Conference 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 5a)
- Harvard University--June 10-24, 1980, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 5b)
- Munich PSSI Aug. 25-26, 1980, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Kyoto Conference 1981, PSSI, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 7a)
- 4th Tokyo Conference, 1981, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 7b)
- Boston Conferences--1980, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- UMEA Conference 1981, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- UMEA Conference 1981, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Tsukuba Conference 1981, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- PSSI Conference: Philadelphia, Nov. 1981, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Geneva Conference PSSI 1981, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Barcelona Conference 1981, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- PSSI: 19th European PSSI Conference Reading, England--Aug. 28-Sept. 1, 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- International Students Assoc., Cincinnati, 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- PSSI: 18th North American Peace Science Conference--College Park, Maryland, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- PSSI Conference--Urbana, Nov. 1983, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Groning--EN, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Input-Output Study-- Data Tables (Box 50, Folder 1)
- 1942 Summer, Washington, D.C.--Brazil Research (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Inter-regional Coefficients for Cotton, 1947 WI with Kavesh, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Regional and Interregional Input-Output Analysis: A Model of a Space Economy, ~1950 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Sheets on Data Derivation--1939, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Input-Output Tables and Notes 1939,1947, 1939, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Regional & Interregional Input-Output Analysis, Walter Isard, Harvard Economic Research Project (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Notes incl. 'Disarmament, Foreign Aid & Economic Growth by Wassily Leontief, edited by WI, 1952-1952 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Input-Output Notes, Committee on Regional Input-Output Studies, 1966, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- research Ideas & Proposals--WI, while associated with Leontif (Box 50, Folder 10)
- WI work while with Leontif in ? (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Regional Development--Input-Output-Outide Materials, Jan.-Feb. 1950, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Atomic Power 1 (Box 50, Folder 13a)
- Atomic Energy Lectures--Teaching Institute, American Univ. 1948-1949, 1948-1950 (Box 50, Folder 13b)
- Atomic Power 2 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Atomic Power 3, 1948-1950 (Box 50, Folder 15A)
- Atomic Power 4, 1945-1947 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- 2nd Annual Conference, Atomic Energy In Industry, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Atomic Power 5 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Atomic Power 6 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Atomic Power 7 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- A Report on Steel and Related Industrial and Population Growth: NY-Trenton-Philadelphia Metro Regions, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- A Report on Steel and Related Industrial and Population Growth: NY-Trenton-Philadelphia Metro Regions, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Maps & Notes (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Thesis (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Population Analysis (Box 50, Folder 25)
- The Impact of Steel on the Greater New York--Philadelphia Urban-industrial Region WI & Robert Kuenne (Box 50, Folder 26a)
- Steel Study 1951-1952 (Box 50, Folder 26b)
- Australian Sect. PSSI (Box 51, Folder 1)
- British Section RSA 1973-1976, 1972-1976 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- British Section RSA 1976-77, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- British Section PSSI 1973, 1971-1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- British Section PSSI 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- British Section PSSI 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Indian Section RSA 1974, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Japan Section PSSI 1973, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Central Europe--PSSI, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Japan --Environmental Conference, 1974-1976 RSA, 1973-1976 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- PSS(I)--Japan -East Asia 1974, 1972-1974 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- PSS(I)--Midwest Meetings, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Munster, 1977, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- NE PSSI Ottawa 1975, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- NE PSSI--Binghamton 1978, Syracuse, May 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- NE Syracuse & Bingingham PSSI, 1973, 1972-1974 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Pacific Region (Manila, Tokyo) 1975, RSA, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- South Asia Section PSSI- 1975, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- South Asia Section PSSI- 1974, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- South Asia 1972, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- South Asia Section PSSI, Oct. 1972- Sept. 1976, 1972-1976 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Southern Section PSSI-- 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Southern Section PSSI 1976-77, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Stockholm-Snickiars 1977, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Western Section PSSI, 1971-1978 (Box 51, Folder 25a)
- W.U. Krakow- Aug 1977 RSA, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- World University Study Series, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- W.U. Conference Rotterdam 1979, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- W.U. Conference India, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 29)
- World Univ.--Feb. 1977 on, 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 30)
- World Univ. Conf.--Japan Norikura, 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Novosibirsk 1976-77--Moscow, 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 32)
- Office Budget and WAAS Income, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 33)
- Man/Environment Prospects, MEST Publication, 1978-1980 (Box 51, Folder 34)
- MEST Promotion, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 35)
- World University Study Series, 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 36)
- World University --By-Laws (Box 51, Folder 37)
- World University Advisory Board, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 38)
- WU--Post-Doctoral Program, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 39)
- ICAAS Revenues & Expends. Account Book, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  International Congress of Arts and Sciences
- WRCI By-Laws, Tax Exempt Notice, 1977-1980 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  World Research Center, Inc.
- WRCI--Taxes-Federal 1977-78, 1969-1976 (Box 51, Folder 42)
- World Univ., Cambridge, MA Operations, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 43)
- Original of 1st Article, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Original of 2nd Article (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Original of 3rd Article (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Original part IV of Summary article, pages 1-80 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Original part IV of Summary article, pages 80-156 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- 4th Summary Article (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Introduction & Conclusions (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Original 1st Summary Article (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Original 2nd Summary Article (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Original 3rd Summary Article (Box 52, Folder 10)
- 2nd Summary Chapter, Book Table of Contents (Box 52, Folder 11)
- 3rd Chapter Materials (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Papers, Alphabetized A-D, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  Student
- Papers Alphabetized E-K, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Papers Alphabetized L-M, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Funck, Newman, Nijkamp--Papers, Alphabetized to R (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Papers, Alphabetized S-Z (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Notes--World Congress, June 1980, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  Draft of papers
- The World System & Behaviour At Its Many Levels: An Integrative Presentation of Approaches (Box 52, Folder 19)
  Draft
- Program--International Congress of Arts & Sciences of the World Univ. (Box 52, Folder 20)
  First World Peace Science Congress
- Man, Environment, Space and Time--Fall 1979, Vol.1, No.1, 1979 (Box 52, Folder Item 21)
  Journal
- Man, Environment, Space and Time--Spring 1981, Vol.1, No.2, 1981 (Box 52, Folder Item 22)
- Man, Environment, Space and Time--Spring 1982, Vol.2, No.1, 1982 (Box 52, Folder Item 23)
- Man, Environment, Space and Time--Fall 1982, Vol.2, No.2, 1982 (Box 52, Folder Item 24)
- Man, Environment, Space and Time--Spring 1983, Vol.3, No.1, 1983 (Box 52, Folder Item 25)
- Man, Environment, Space and Time--Fall 1983, Vol.3, No.2, 1983 (Box 52, Folder Item 26)
- Man, Environment, Space and Time--Spring 1984, Vol.4, No.1, 1984 (Box 52, Folder Item 27)
- Man, Environment, Space and Time--Spring 1988, Vol.5, No.1, 1988 (Box 52, Folder Item 28)
- A (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- B (1976-1977), 1975-1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- C (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- D (1976-1977), 1975-1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- E (1976-1977), 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- F (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- G (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- H (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- I (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- J (1976-1977), 1973-1977 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- K (1976-1977), 1975-1978 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- L (1976-1977), 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- M (1976-1977), 1975-1978 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- N (1976-1977), 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- O (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- P (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Q (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- R (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- S (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- T (1976-1977), 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- U (1976-1977), 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- V (1976-1977), 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- W (1976-1977), 1975-1978 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- X-Z(1976-1977), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 24)
- A (1975-1976), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- B (1975), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- C (1975-1976), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- D (1975), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- E (1975), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- F (1975), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- G (1975), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- H (1975), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- I (1975), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- J (1975), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- K (1975), 1970-1977 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- L (1975), 1975-1977 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- M (1975), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- N (1975), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- O (1975), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- P (1975), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Q-R (1975), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- S (1975), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- T (1975), 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- U (1975), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- V (1975), 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- W (1975), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- X-Z (1975), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- A (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- B (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 25)
- C (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 26)
- D ( 1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 27)
- E (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 28)
- F (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 29)
- G (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 30)
- H (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 31)
- I (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 32)
- J (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 33)
- K(1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 34)
- L (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 35)
- M(1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 36)
- N (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 37)
- O (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 38)
- P (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 39)
- Q-R (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 40)
- S (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 41)
- T (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 42)
- U-V (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 43)
- W (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 44)
- XYZ (1974), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, Re: USSR 1963-1965, 1963-1965 (Box 54, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, Re: Moscow Visit 1968, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, Misc. 1959-1984, 1959-1984 (Box 54, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, Misc. 1975-1978 (Pt.1), 1975-1978 (Box 54, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, Misc. 1975-1978 (Pt.2), 1974-1978 (Box 54, Folder 50)
- Regional Science and Planning--June 1980, WU World Congress (A-Z), 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- WU Peace Science Frist Congress--June 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Int'l Congress--Other, June 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Applicants for Post-Dr. Study in Regional Science, 1968-1971 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- WI Paper March 1978-June 1980 (1), 1978-1980 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- WI Paper march 1978-June 1981 (2), 1978-1980 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Multiple Growth Pole Paper--RSA, Nov. 1977, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- WI Paper Aug. 1976-Dec. 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Nobel Symposium Paper, 1976, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- WI Papers 1972-June 1976, 1954-1976 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Economics of War & Peace, Wilmington--Nov. 1967, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Isard & Chatterji--Sept. 1967, Calcutta, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Isard & Czamanski 1966, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- NASA St. Louis Conference 1964, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Power w/K. Deutch 1964, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Isard & Wolpert--Ghent, July 1964, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Preface--Japanese Edition of Location & Space Economy, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Isard & Schooler--Local & Regional Impacts, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Isard & Schooler--Dec. 1963, Boston, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Participation Potential Paper--Pittsburgh, Tokyo, Lund (1962-1963), 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 16)